winningwp.com 2017-06-06

# WinningWP Privacy Policy - WinningWP

This privacy policy sets out how WinningWP uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.

WinningWP is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

WinningWP may occasionally change this policy by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from: January 2013.

## What we collect:

We may collect the following information:

  * name and contact information, such as email address
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
  * non-personal information regarding how users interact with our site

## What we do with the information we gather:

We collect this information in order to better understand your needs, which in turn allows us to improve our content and services. We may also collect your information for any of the follow reasons:

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

## How we protect your information

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have adopted suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Sharing your information

We do not sell, trade, or rent user’s personal information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the site and/or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys.

## Web-browser cookies

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that cookie.

## What do cookies do?

Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improve the user experience. They can also help to ensure that adverts you see online are more relevant to you and your interests. The cookies used on this website include the following types of cookies:

### Strictly necessary cookies

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies services you have asked for, like shopping baskets or e-billing, cannot be provided.

### Performance cookies

These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.

### Functionality cookies

These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. For instance, a website may be able to provide you with local weather reports or traffic news by storing in a cookie the region in which you are currently located. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. 

### Advertising cookies

These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organizations.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Changes to this privacy policy

WinningWP has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date displayed at the bottom of this page. We encourage users Users to frequently check this page for any changes in order to stay informed on issues such as how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibilty to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of any modifications.

By using this site, it is deemed you have agreed to these terms and conditions of use. If at any time you choose not to accept these terms and conditions of use, please do not continue to use this site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

If you have any questions regarding our policies, the practices of this website, or your dealings with WinningWP, please [contact us](https://winningwp.com/contact/).

**_This document was last updated on January 21, 2014_**
